Contact Details

8623801495

srm9522@gmail.com

Education

- Bsc.IT from Parle Tilak Vidyalaya Association Sathaye College, Vile Parle(E), Mumbai-400057 (Aug-2017)
- HSC from Bhavanishankar Jr.
 College of Science, Dadar(W),
 Mumbai-400028 (Feb-2013)
- SSC from Topivala Pushpapark
 Marathi School, Malad(E), Mumbai 400097 (March-2011)

Skills

- HTML5
- CSS
- Bootstrap
- Javascript
- Jquery

Certifications



Shweta Mane

Professional Summary

Having 5 Years of Experience in developing APIs, Web & Rest APIs, Windows & Console based applications. Experience in .Net Core APIs, Asp.Net with Web forms, Windows Applications, C#, Console, VB.net, Web Services, HTML, C, C++, Jquery, Javascript.

Total Years of Experience

• 5 Years

Experience

1. Software Engineer

Brainvire Infotech Pvt Ltd (Client: IIFL Finance)

June 2022 - Present

• Design, develop and maintain backend components and services using .NET technologies, collaborate with team members, troubleshoot and resolve issues, participate in testing activities.

2. Software Engineer

Clover Infotech Pvt Ltd (Client: HDFC Bank)

June 2021 - June 2022

• Design, develop, and maintain in-house portals using ASP.NET technologies, implement new features, manage databases using MS-SQL Server, optimize database queries.

3. Jr. Software Developer

Greybits Technologies

September 2018 - May 2021

• Independently implement and develop features for Billing Software and Desktop Version Gym Software, conduct unit testing, collaborate with team members, document code and processes.

Contact Details

8623801495

srm9522@gmail.com

Education

- Bsc.IT from Parle Tilak Vidyalaya Association Sathaye College, Vile Parle(E), Mumbai-400057 (Aug-2017)
- HSC from Bhavanishankar Jr.
 College of Science, Dadar(W),
 Mumbai-400028 (Feb-2013)
- SSC from Topivala Pushpapark
 Marathi School, Malad(E), Mumbai 400097 (March-2011)

Skills

- HTML5
- CSS
- Bootstrap
- Javascript
- Jquery

Certifications

Project Details

1. Trade Terminal (IIFL Finance)

• Design, develop, and maintain backend components and services using .NET technologies for a financial trading platform.

Technologies Used: Web services, .NET Core APIs, MS-Sql

2. Gemfind (Diamond Market)

• Design, develop, and implement backend APIs for a diamond market platform using Dot Net Core technology.

Technologies Used: Dot Net Core API, MS-Sql

3. Trade Finance (HDFC)

• Design, develop, and maintain in-house portals for trade finance using ASP.NET technologies.

Technologies Used: Web services, API, Windows applications, Console applications

4. Billing Software, Desktop Version Gym Software

 Develop billing software and desktop version gym software using ASP.NET Web Forms and VB.NET Web Forms.

Technologies Used: Web services, Web-forms, windows, console, VB.net, MS-Sql